theauteurs.com 2009-06-16

# Privacy Policy

The Auteurs’ Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using The Auteurs, located at http://www.theauteurs.com and its directly associated domains and social network presence (collectively, "The Auteurs" or "Website"). 

By using or accessing The Auteurs, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact our privacy staff at support@theauteurs.com. 

## The Information We Collect

When you visit the Auteurs you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Website use information collected by us as you interact with our Website. 

When you register with The Auteurs, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us. 

When you enter The Auteurs, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all The Auteurs visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to The Auteurs. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 

When you use The Auteurs, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, add applications, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. 

You post your own private or personal information on the Website at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that information you post on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of user information may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your information. 

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email or instant message inviting him or her to visit the site. The Auteurs stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at info@theauteurs.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

The Auteurs may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the The Auteurs service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. 

By using The Auteurs, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to the United States of America and processed. 

## Use of Information Obtained by The Auteurs

When you register with The Auteurs, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the networks specified in your privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on the Auteurs. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by The Auteurs that we think you may find valuable. 

Profile information is used by The Auteurs primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e.g., posting to your wall), other The Auteurs users may be able to supplement your profile. 

Profile information you submit to The Auteurs will be available to users of The Auteurs who belong to at least one of the networks you allow to access the information through your privacy settings (e.g., school, geography, friends of friends). Your name, network names, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the The Auteurs network and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a friend request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (friend, friend of friend, member of your networks, etc.) that allows such access based on your privacy settings. 

The Auteurs may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message or poke, or someone posts on your wall, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact. 

Generally, you may opt out of such emails here, though The Auteurs reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications. 

The Auteurs may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like a band or movie and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you The Auteurs. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put a favorite movie in your profile, we might serve you an advertisement highlighting a screening of a similar one in your town. But we don't tell the movie company who you are. 

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to Social Network Platforms where we have a presence, newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, Social Network Platform developers and other users of The Auteurs, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile (e.g., removing photo tag links). 

## Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We allow you to choose the information you provide to friends and networks through The Auteurs. Our network architecture and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your information. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. When you use The Auteurs, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, listings or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, listings or other items , this information may become publicly available. 

## Links

The Auteurs may contain links to other websites or be accessed through other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by The Auteurs. 

## Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on The Auteurs are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. The Auteurs does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on The Auteurs unless you choose to share it with them. 

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by The Auteurs and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers. 

## Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on The Auteurs is readily available through the profile editing tools. The Auteurs users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their The Auteurs account may do so, on the My Auteurs or Login page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of the Auteurs. 

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on The Auteurs, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another The Auteurs user) you generally cannot remove such communications. 

## Security

The Auteurs takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). (To learn more about SSL, go to http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer). Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. 

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of The Auteurs, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at info@theauteurs.com. You may also contact us by mail at 139 Forest Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94301.
